Love Shiga-san, our days are numbered
Even if one day it will come to an end.
Okay.
Yes!
So that's it.
Yes, sir.
Um, Sasaki Anri...
Yes.
I tried on Ishin Aihara's makeup.
I'd like to introduce some new cosmetics that are very lukewarm.
I'd like to do that.
Can I use a pompadour for a moment?
You looked like you just paid me, so I'll let you go.
That's okay.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Yes, please.
Okay, let's do it.
Thank you very much for watching.
We'll start with the eyebrows.
Eyebrows.
Kate.
This is the one we showed you last time.
Yes, ma'am.
This is Kate.
This is the
This is the &B brush.
This one is really nice.
It's a little bit slanted and thin.
so...
What?
It's hard to do every time.
Yeah, it's...
It's hard.
Yes, it is.
I'm the type.
It doesn't stick out too much, so it's easy to adjust.
It's easy to adjust, so that's what I'd like to do.
Oh, by the way, my eyebrows are brown.
Yes, I have brown eyebrows.
No, don't budge them, okay?
Wait a minute, this is a little bit of that.
I'll do my best.
I think it's an act.
I think my eyebrows are just...
The human form?
I'll show you.
Okay.
Not too thick.
Yeah. - Mm-hm.
Shoe.
If he gets depressed, even if it's just a little bit, it's not good.
I can't go on, can I?
That's what I was thinking when I saw this.
Are you going?
It's hard to tell with the camera, but I think it looks a little nicer in the mirror.
Now let's do the opposite.
How do you like your eyebrows? They're definitely a little bit thicker.
It's definitely a little thicker. Yes, it's a bit like letting the original shape shine through.
Next, I would like to apply eyebrow mascara.
Eyebrow mascara? I'd like to apply mascara to my eyebrows.
They're out of focus.
Okay, then. Snake Eyebrow Mascara.
Heavy rotation.
Ash gray.
Like a hazard between black and brown.
It fits everyone.
2. try different colors
3. try a different color
Oh, isn't it nice?
I wouldn't put that much on.
It's definitely a little darker.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow!
That's great. - That's really great.
Next! The all-important buehler!
This is me, I'm a straight-edge curler, but...
I was hoping you could do the curler for me.
Oh, by myself.
Yes, yes, yes.
But I'll give you some guidance.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
I brought a mirror today.
Thank you.
Now, let's start with this.
I'm going to start by holding down... holding down...
Hold the root...
Oh, the root? That's it.
Oh, okay.
Very crease, crease, crease.
Okay.
And then, "Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Giggle, giggle, giggle.
Raise the root straight up.
Like this?
Keep it straight.
If you do it like this...
It will point straight up.
And then, while doing it like this...
Ging-in, ging-in.
Yes, sir.
I want you to go straight up, just as if you were going straight up.
Go straight up
Up, up, up!
Can I talk to you now?
Can I talk now?
That's pretty good.
Looking good, sweetie.
I'm gonna put this on right now.
If you're going to apply it right away, do you want to do it yourself?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Like mascara.
And this one, you just start at the root and go in, in, in, in, in, in.
Like this, jagged.
Jagged.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
And this one right here at the front of the eye.
And then, you can apply a lot of paint to the crease.
Like this?
How do you like it?
I think it looks good.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Oh, keep going! Keep going!
Uh, yeah! Have fun!
Up, up, up.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Up, up, up, up.
Up, up, up.
Pretty much straight up.
Just do it like this in this state.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
ping pong
Ping, ping, ping.
It's up?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, okay.
Why do we have to do this right away?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly.
speedy, speedy, speedy, speedy
Go, go, go, go, go.
Okay, what kind of brow mascara is this?
It's, uh, oh, I forgot to introduce it again.
It's Elegance Curl Lash Fixer.
Elegance?
Elegance.
The staying power is amazing!
The key is to do it right after you use your eyelash curler.
You know, when you use an eyelash curler, after a while, it kind of goes down.
How do you like it? Your eyelashes look great....
Your lashes look really nice.
Grab the base of the lashes, and then grab the crease.
The crease?
Grab the crease, the crease right here.
Make a semicircle, like this.
Like this?
Yes, yes, yes! Like this, slowly fizz like this.
Like a semicircle.
Lower it, please.
But that's okay.
A little lower.
Okay. - Okay.
Oh, we have to do it right away.
Yeah, right away, right away, right away.
Oh, no, look.
Speed game! Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly!
Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly
Go, go, go, go, go!
Here we go.
This one, too... Oh, let's do this one, shall we?
Yes, I'll do it.
My hand hurts.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Just a little more this way?
No?
No, it's not.
Like this?
Yes, sir.
What?
No, sir.
This way.
It's the middle finger.
What?
Like this.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Like that.
The crease.
Crease it.
Very crease.
Crease, crease, crease.
Okay, okay.
You got it?
I got it.
That was fast.
There you go.
Perfect for a heatless bath.
Thank you
Squeeeeeeeeeee!
That's about right?
All right, let's get back on track.
All right, let's see.
I'm gonna pinch it.
Very close to the root.
Right at the corner of the eye.
Right at the base of the eye.
Yes, sir.
Yes, as you draw
Yes, yes...
Uy...
Yes, be conscious
Real conscious, real conscious, real conscious
Here we go
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good
Speed up!
I'm sorry, sir, you're too slow.
Jagged edge of the eye.
I gave it back pretty good.
I'll give it back. Shogun.
It's a gang bang.
I'm already feeling like the lashes are challenging.
Now I'd like to move on to the next eye.
I'm going to use the Clio eyeshadow palette.
This is Clio.
This is the one on the far left.
I'm going to use the brown color.
It's called "Deca-eye effect".
If you apply it to the crease here under the eyes
It makes your eyes look bigger.
I see.
That's right!
So it's very good for you.
I'll do it.
I'll do it, please.
I'd like to have a hair ball for an eye, please.
I really love this one
I don't want to be without it
I have to have this for my eyes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, too.
Right eye okay?
It's really dark over here.
That's it.
Wait, there's one there, too.
Raise your hand if you've reached your limit by now.
Like a good delivery or something.
I'll take it. Raise your hand.
Please.
Yes, sir.
What the hell?
You look like you're in a funk.
It's the eyelashes, isn't it?
Okay. How's it feel?
Yeah, it feels like there's a lot in here.
A little.
Yuzumi.
I'm fine.
Okay.
And then...
Oh, it shows up.
This is the Lien Da Beauty eyeshadow palette.
This is my current favorite.
It's my current favorite.
There's a brand called Lien Da.
It's called "Lien Da Beauty".
They also offer cosmetics.
Which color is this?
This orange one.
Pull this out first.
Okay.
On the eyelid.
The point of this is...
The point of this is that you want to put it only in the double-exposed area
The point is to put it only in the double width part.
If you do the upper part
If you do the upper part, it might make you look puffy.
Or the whole eyehall.
Yes, yes, yes.
Only the double-exposed area.
I'll apply it.
Looks good.
And the other way around.
Yeah.
Looks good.
Then, next, I'm going to apply a little bit of orange lame on the bottom right here.
It's very shiny.
I'm going to put it over the orange laminate, and then I'm going to put it over the orange laminate.
And then, pirin...
I'm going to apply the most glittery glitter on the top right.
There is a point.
I want to paint the center of the eyeballs darkly.
Around the center of the eyeball, I'm going to apply the glitter lightly.
Since this is glitter, I'm going to apply it very lightly on the eyelid.
It looks great!
What do you think? Let her see.
One time on the upper eyelid.
What do you think?
Wow!
It's like closing your eyes.
Okay, then.
How does it feel?
I'm not sure.
Okay, let's do the bottom.
First, the base under the base is also orange.
The base under the base is also orange.
Base under the base is also orange.
Pink! Now we'll use pink.
Much darker.
This is from the corner of the eye to the middle of the eye.
Apply only about half of it.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Got it.
It's pink.
The pink might have rubbed off a little bit, but I don't know.
It looks good.
Okay. - Okay.
Now I want to apply the glitter here.
The key to applying glitter to the tear ducts is to make the glitter darker at the top of the eye.
The point of glitter on the tear troughs is to make the inner corner of the eyes darker.
What do you think?
How is it?
When I look at it in the mirror, it's getting more and more glittery.
That's right.
And then we'll put glitter here, too.
I see.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it is.
How do you like it?
That's it for the eyeshadow.
Is that it?
That's it.
Next.
Teleriren.
Terelle, terelle, terelle, terelle.
This is Sezanne's two different eyeliners.
I use it to make tear troughs.
I don't have tear troughs, so I use it to make tear troughs.
I don't have much either.
No, I have quite a few.
You have tear troughs?
Make the most of it.
Do you have them?
I'd like to make the most of it.
Excuse me...
Yes, sir.
Just enough to make it stand out?
Yes.
Yes!
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's good, that's pretty good.
He says your eyes are almost done.
Okay, next.
Eyeliner.
This is called tattoo eyeliner.
This is the one that matches my eyes the best.
It doesn't come off easily.
It's like an excellent channel.
It goes right along the person's eyes.
I'm going to draw along the person's eyes.
I'm going to do my line.
The line is very thick.
Next, I'm going to draw the upper mucous membrane line.
We'll draw the upper mucous membrane line.
Mucous membrane line? What's that?
Mucosa.
Right there.
And there, too.
That's the one you drew on the bottom.
It also makes the eyes clearer.
It makes your eyes clear.
I used Cammake's
Creamy Touch Liner
I use it.
Part by part.
Does it change things?
What do you call it?
Is that a pencil?
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know, I don't know.
Let's take a look at this.
Excuse me.
Come here.
You're right, it's totally different.
Right?
Don't you like it?
It's amazing.
What do you think?
It's a bald spot...
Now, let's use these two items.
It's done, so...
Maybelline.
Maybelline Sky High.
Finishing mascara.
I think I'll have you do the top one.
It's a mascara with jagged edges.
So I'm going to do the top.
So I'm going to do this one right here in the middle.
Just like that.
Just like before.
Jagged from the eye
A jagged edge from the eye
It's ridiculously long.
Yes, it's a mess.
It's a mess.
Yes, sir.
How do you like it? It's not bad, is it?
Now let's do the bottom one. Do the same on the bottom.
OK!
How's it look?
Oh!
Are the eyes done? Maybe it's...
My eyes are done.
That's crazy.
Now it's time to continue with the shape.
This is the nose shadow.
I'm going to use the same one I used for the eyebrows earlier.
Now for the nose shadow.
I'm going to use the brush that comes with this.
I'm going to use the brush that comes with the nose shadow.
and the light brown in the middle.
Just dab it on and dab it on.
It's really light.
Right here on the nose.
I apply it lightly all over.
Just a little bit.
Can you spread it by hand?
It's fine.
Or you can just put it inside.
Down there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it looks good.
So, highlights.
Highlight.
Long and 01.
The bridge of the nose and the tip of the nose
I would like to apply it on the top of the mouth and the bottom of the mouth
Yes, please.
Yes, ma'am.
And finally, the nose shadow.
Shading?
I'm already bald, but I don't want to talk about that, so...
It's Cezanne's shading.
This is number 01.
I'm going to apply this neck shade to the face line.
Here.
I'm going to put it in from in front of the ear.
And look here.
And the nose shadow on the nose, which I just put in, I'm going to apply lightly.
And the lip shadow?
Just the lips.
And then...
And...
ROM&D
No. 04, right?
Number 04.
Yeah, like this.
Okay, so you take this in your hand, and you just...
And pump it on the inside.
Like this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, uh, and blend it with the top.
Okay. - Mm-hmm.
Does it look good?
It's good.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
You can see it inside and out.
This one!
This is also tinted gloss.
Tinted gloss
It's so pretty and puffy.
It's so cute and puffy!
It's so cute!
Just dab it all over the place...
Yeah, it looks good.
Does it look good?
Yeah, it's good.
It's done!
Over the thorny path!
Yeah!
How is it?
It's great!
It's so different from the usual, I'm surprised.
Oh, my gosh!
Do you want to let your hair down?
How do you like it?
Wow.
Snap, snap, snap!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Squeeze time.
Here you go.
What do you think?
I haven't changed much.
I'm the main one who's changed.
I really have.
It's not easy being a girl.
It's a long process.
There are so many different items
So many items.
Even today, I can't remember how to do it.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it...
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it
That's what I'm saying
I don't have much time, so I made it up!
See you next time
I'll do your makeup, hair, clothes, etc.
I'll do your hair, clothes, etc.
Bye bye!
Thank you very much.